(Sheldon-bot:)You're in my spot.
(Sheldon-bot:)This may seem a little odd
at first,
(Sheldon-bot:)but over time,
you'll grow accustomed
(Sheldon-bot:)to dealing with me
in this configuration.
(Penny:)Yeah, to be honest, I
don't see much difference.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon-bot:)That's what I was going for.
(Sheldon-bot:)Now, Leonard, tomorrow,
when we go to work,
(Sheldon-bot:)you'll need to allow
some extra time
(Sheldon-bot:)to get me down the stairs.
(Sheldon-bot:)For your convenience,
I disassemble into four pieces.
(Leonard:)This is ridiculous.
(Leonard:)I'm coming to talk to you.
(Sheldon-bot:)You don't know where I am.
(Sheldon-bot:)My physical body
is safely ensconced
(Sheldon-bot:)in a secure,
undisclosed location.
(Leonard:)You're in your bedroom.
(Sheldon-bot:)No, I'm not.
(Leonard:)I can hear your voice
coming from your bedroom.